Address: Building no. 9, Flat No.65, Sector 3, CGS, Antop Hill, Mumbai.

■ C: 09315345172 ■amartya.wipr@gmail.com

Title

LL.B.in commercial laws from Law School, Banaras Hindu University, Varanasi seeking legal profile for handling legal matters more specifically related to copyright, Trademarks and other commercial law.

Professional Summary

Enthusiastic Legal professional versed in Copyright, trademarks and others Commercial laws with Post Qualification Experience (PQE) of more than 3 year currently working as Examiner of Trademark in ,Ministry of Commerce and Industry, Government of India, Mumbai.

Experience

1. .Examiner of Trademark ,DIPP, Ministry of Commerce and Industry,Mumbai(Contractual): 15 April 2019 to 2 Januaryr 2021

Nature of work: Legal drafting and review of various trademark

and copyrights agreement.

Description of Work: Examination and drafting of various Trademark and copyright agreement, production agreement, artist agreement, music license agreement, content acquisition agreement, contract and assignment deed, and various copyright related documents and also taking part in court matters relating to copyright and trademark office at Mumbai

2. Legal Assistant, Copyrights office, DIPP, Ministry of Commerce and Industry (Contractual): 17 April 2017 to 31/03/2019

Nature of work: Legal drafting and review of various copyrights agreement.

Description of Work: Examination and drafting of various copyright agreement, production agreement, artist agreement, music license agreement, content acquisition agreement, contract and assignment deed and various copyright related documents and also taking part in court matters relating to copyright office.

3. Abhishek Agarwal , Advocate on Record, Supreme Court of India as Junior Advocate

Duration: 28/07/2016 to 14/04/2017 **Nature of Work**: Commercial Law

Major Areas: drafting notice of oppositions, counter statements, reply, *counter* reply, vetting of various commercial agreements, purchase agreements, assignment deeds, license deeds etc.

Skills

- Legal/non-Legal Research
- Active listener
- M.S. office
- Public speaking expertise
- Strong research skills

Education

LL.B, Law (2013 - 2016)

Law school, Banaras Hindu University, Varanasi.

Percentage: 58.30%

B.Com. (2010-2013)

C. S. J. M. University Kanpur

Percentage: 52.84

XII (Senior Secondary), Science

Year of Completion: 2010

I.S.C. Board

(New Vision School, Raebareli (U.P., India)

Percentage: 66.33%

X (Secondary)

Year of Completion: 2008

U.P. Board

(New Standard Public School, Raebareli, U.P., India)

Percentage: 51.33%

Internships

INTERN

Corporate Legal Partners - New Delhi

01/12/2015 to31/12/2015

- Did extensive case law and statutory law research on various commercial laws.
- Drafted reply, counter reply, affidavit, and plaint for law firm.
- Handled various queries from foreign clients related to Indian companies law etc.
- Making notes for arguments and drafting.

Hon'ble Justice Imtiyaz Murtaza, Senior Judge, High Court of judicature at Allahabad 10/06/2014 to15/07/2014

- Worked with the standing council of government of UttarPradesh.
- Assisted in drafting and review of appeals, wills and contracts.
- Observed day to day court proceedings in court no.3 and made notes for assistance of Lordship.
- Review of legal documents such as pleadings, appeals, wills and contract.

Certifications

- WIPO ACADEMY: General Course on Intellectual Property(**DL101**)
- WORLD BANK: Course on Software Licensing form World Bank
- Enrolled with Bar Council of Delhi State Bar Council from **December 2016[D/1643/16]**
- Cleared AIBE X- All India Bar Examination 10 (COP/2017/152751)

Other interests

Internet Surfing and Reading English Literature, Outdoor Games, Playing Musical Instruments

Languages

Fluent – English, Hindi

Personal Information

Father's Name: Mr. Radhey Shyam Pandey

Mother's Name: Mrs. Sadhana Pandey

Father's/Mother's Occupation: Teacher

Hometown: Raebareli

DateofBirth [DD/MM/YY]: 18/05/1994.